<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
      xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
      version="3.5"
      xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd">
   <titleInfo>
      <title>Bedford County Fair Stock Certificate</title>
   </titleInfo>
   <typeOfResource>still image</typeOfResource>
   <genre authority="dct">still image</genre>
   <genre>stock certificates</genre>
   <subject>
      <topic>Stock certificates.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>County fairs.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Bedford County (Tenn.) History.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <geographic>Shelbyville (Tenn.) -- Centennial Celebrations, Etc.</geographic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Trade, Business, and Industry.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Popular Culture and Folklife.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <geographic>The Emergence of Modern America (1890-1930).</geographic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <geographic>Tennessee -- Bedford County.</geographic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Postcards.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Bedford County Fair Association.</topic>
   </subject>
   <note>2 tifs. One stock certificate for the Bedford County Fair Association of Shelbyville, Tennessee made to I.G. Miller. It is a square stock printed in green and black with an elaborate border encasing a depiction of justice, seated with her scales and a dagger. Two other women recline at her feet. Below the scene is printed the text "Shares $25.00 each. Number 216. Shares one. Bedford County Fair Association. Shelbyville, Tennessee. This is to Certify that I. G. Miller is the owner of --one-- Shares of the Capital Stock of Bedford County Fair Association transferable only on the Books of Corporation in person or by Attorney on surrender of this Certificate. In Witness Whereof, the duly authorized officers of this Corporation have hereunto subscribed their names and fused the corporate Seal to be hereto affixed at Shelbyville this 26th day of Septembre A.D. 1904. SFB Gowan, secretary. JM Shofner, President." An eagle is printed at the bottom of the stock and holds a banner reading "E. Pluribus Unum." The second image is the verso and was printed with brown ink, and is organized into three parts. The verso has a similar border but is more graphic than the front. This side reads "Certificate for Shares of the Capital Stock of Bedford County Fair Association Issued to. Dated. For value received hereby sell transfer and assign to...Shares of Stock within mentioned and hereby authorize...to make the necessary transfer on the Books of the Corporation. Witness...hand and seal this...day of...19...Witnessed by..."</note>
   <note>The University of Tennessee Libraries (Knoxville, Tennessee) is the digital publisher.</note>
   <identifier type="local">TU:DLC:Filename:0081_000050_000204_0000</identifier>
   <relatedItem>
      <titleInfo>
         <title>Digital Collection: The Growth of Democracy in Tennessee: A Grassroots Approach to Volunteer Voices</title>
      </titleInfo>
   </relatedItem>
   <language>
      <languageTerm type="code">eng</languageTerm>
   </language>
   <accessCondition type="use and reproduction"
                    xlink:href="http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/">Copyright Undetermined</accessCondition>
   <location>
      <url access="object in context" usage="primary display">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A12075</url>
      <url access="preview">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A12075/datastream/TN/view</url>
   </location>
   <recordInfo>
      <recordContentSource>University of Tennessee, Knoxville. Libraries</recordContentSource>
      <languageOfCataloging>
         <languageTerm authority="iso639-2b" type="code">eng</languageTerm>
      </languageOfCataloging>
      <recordOrigin>Created and edited in general conformance to MODS Guidelines (Version 3.5).</recordOrigin>
   </recordInfo>
</mods>