<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="3.5" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd"><titleInfo><title>Ann Eliza King in Plainfield, North Carolina, to James M. King in Davidson County, Tennessee</title></titleInfo><typeOfResource>text</typeOfResource><genre authority="dct">text</genre><genre>letters (correspondence)</genre><subject><topic>Mate selection.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Communication in the family.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Death -- Religious aspects.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Family Life and Gender Relations.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Women.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Religion.</topic></subject><subject><geographic>Expansion and Reform (1801-1861).</geographic></subject><subject><geographic>Tennessee -- Rutherford County.</geographic></subject><note>Ann Eliza King of North Carolina wrote to her cousin James M. King of Davidson County, Tennessee encouraging him in his quest to find a wife. He apparently had lost his first choice, but planned to continue to search for a suitable wife. She expressed her joy at the news, noting that their family had enough bachelors in it already. She has kept her eye out for a likely candidate for him in her area, but noted that none of the girls she saw at church would suit him. She wrote of some relatives who have died, noting that "our loss is there ineffable gain, they are in the bosome of their father and their God." Towards the end of the letter, she responded to a comment of his that his journey home was long and lonesome, expressing the hope that his next journey would be shortened by the company of a "lovely and affectionate wife."</note><note>The University of Tennessee Libraries (Knoxville, Tennessee) is the digital publisher.</note><identifier type="local">TU:DLC:Filename:0039_000050_000201_0000</identifier><relatedItem><titleInfo><title>Digital Collection: The Growth of Democracy in Tennessee: A Grassroots Approach to Volunteer Voices</title></titleInfo></relatedItem><language><languageTerm type="code">eng</languageTerm></language><accessCondition type="use and reproduction" xlink:href="http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/">Copyright Undetermined</accessCondition><location><url access="object in context" usage="primary display">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A6105</url><url access="preview">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A6105/datastream/TN/view</url></location></mods>