<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="3.5" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd"><titleInfo><title>Letter from D.L. Chandler to General H.H. Thomas</title></titleInfo><typeOfResource>text</typeOfResource><genre authority="dct">text</genre><genre>letters</genre><subject><topic>Reconstruction (U.S. history, 1865-1877) Tennessee</topic></subject><subject><geographic>MEMPHIS (TENN.)</geographic></subject><subject><topic>Reconstruction and the freedmen: appearance of hitherto undocumented people in legal records; the fastening of sharecropping on the countryside.</topic></subject><subject><topic>African-Americans.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Government and Politics.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Social Reform.</topic></subject><subject><geographic>Civil War and Reconstruction (1850-1877).</geographic></subject><note>Letter dated May 21, 1867 from D.L. Chandler to General H.H. Thomas. On the letterhead of the "Office of Superintendent Metropolitan Police." Says that Colonel Beaumont was answering one portion of General Thomas`s letter and he the other. States the suspected murderer of Wilson is Thomas W. Knowlton and describes him. Discusses the registration of the voters for the upcoming elections. Says that by polling day there should be 5,500 blacks and 3,200 whites registered, which should give a majority at the poll of 2,500. States that Colonel Stokes made a good impression, "although he has not the tricks of the politician to such a degree as Etheridge...Etheridge gets the shouts and yells, while Stokes carries the votes." Says that the "work at Bartlett`s Station produced good fruit," with the result that 300 blacks were registered. "The meeting was the first one we had had in that vicinity and stirred the darky mind wonderfully..." Says that the party is in good spirits. Wishes that Stokes was less defensive with Etheridge. Urges that he attack him continuously.</note><note>The University of Tennessee Libraries (Knoxville, Tennessee) is the digital publisher.</note><identifier type="local">TU:DLC:Filename:0012_000103_000202_0000</identifier><relatedItem><titleInfo><title>Digital Collection: The Growth of Democracy in Tennessee: A Grassroots Approach to Volunteer Voices</title></titleInfo></relatedItem><language><languageTerm type="code">eng</languageTerm></language><accessCondition type="use and reproduction" xlink:href="http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/">Copyright Undetermined</accessCondition><location><url access="object in context" usage="primary display">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A4606</url><url access="preview">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A4606/datastream/TN/view</url></location></mods>