<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="3.5" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd"><titleInfo><title>Coca-Cola Englewood Bottling Works</title></titleInfo><typeOfResource>still image</typeOfResource><genre authority="dct">still image</genre><genre>black-and-white photographs</genre><subject><topic>Bottling.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Coca-Cola Bottling Company United (U.S.)</topic></subject><subject><topic>Coca-Cola Company.</topic></subject><subject><geographic>Englewood (Tenn.) -- History</geographic></subject><subject><topic>Trade, Business, and Industry.</topic></subject><subject><geographic>The Emergence of Modern America (1890-1930).</geographic></subject><subject><geographic>Tennessee -- McMinn County.</geographic></subject><subject><topic>Photographs.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Coca Cola Englewood Bottling Works.</topic></subject><note>2 tifs. The first image of the Englewood Bottling Works shows five men standing on the porch wearing overalls, aprons and hats. The wooden structure has a large porch and on a taller sign the words "Englewood Bottling Works" have been painted onto clapboard. Through the windows a Coca-Cola symbol can be seen. The second photograph is of the Coca-Cola Englewood Bottling Works. It appears to be the same building as the same photograph, but with a new sign, including the Coca-Cola name and symbol, and in a better state of repair--the woodwork on the front of the store is painted, with the door and window frames in a darker shade than the porch, and the porch roof has been improved. An older man stands on the porch and a young woman in a white dress and an a young man stands at the other end, with the young man on the porch stair. A horse and carriage wait in front of the store with a little boy in a white hat sitting in the shade of the carriage's canopy. Visible behind the store are other small buildings. The Coca-Cola Bottling Works was a major employer in Englewood, Tennessee during the first half of the 20th century.</note><note>The University of Tennessee Libraries (Knoxville, Tennessee) is the digital publisher.</note><identifier type="local">TU:DLC:Filename:0083_000050_000225_0000</identifier><relatedItem><titleInfo><title>Digital Collection: The Growth of Democracy in Tennessee: A Grassroots Approach to Volunteer Voices</title></titleInfo></relatedItem><language><languageTerm type="code">eng</languageTerm></language><accessCondition type="use and reproduction" xlink:href="http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/">Copyright Undetermined</accessCondition><location><url access="object in context" usage="primary display">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A12085</url><url access="preview">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A12085/datastream/TN/view</url></location></mods>