<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="3.5" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd"><titleInfo><title>Buildings at Copperhill in Polk County, Tennessee</title></titleInfo><typeOfResource>still image</typeOfResource><genre authority="dct">still image</genre><genre>color slides</genre><subject><topic>Copperhill (Tenn.)</topic></subject><subject><topic>Copper mining.</topic></subject><subject><geographic>Polk County (Tenn.)</geographic></subject><subject><topic>Farming and Agriculture.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Trade, Business, and Industry.</topic></subject><subject><geographic>Contemporary United States (1968-present).</geographic></subject><subject><geographic>Tennessee -- Polk County.</geographic></subject><subject><topic>Photographs.</topic></subject><note>2 tifs. Images of buildings near the mines in Copperhill, Tennessee in 1970. The first image is of a partially brick, partially aluminum clad home on a barren site. The second image is of a concrete block industrial structure with machinery behind it and dumpsters in the foreground. The devastation of the Copper Basin was so great that the area was once considered the largest man-made biological desert in the nation, with over 50 miles stripped. In the 1870s the mines began to fail due to a lack of transportation and a decline in the quality of ore. However, improvements in transportation over the next twenty years led to rapid growth in the area. Eventually the area's industry shifted to sulfuric acid, which was used to smelt copper. In 1941 the Tennessee Valley Authority began an effort on site to re-vegetate the basin, including the construction of sixteen buildings. The area was mined until 1987.</note><note>The University of Tennessee Libraries (Knoxville, Tennessee) is the digital publisher.</note><identifier type="local">TU:DLC:Filename:0055_000058_000203_0000</identifier><relatedItem><titleInfo><title>Digital Collection: The Growth of Democracy in Tennessee: A Grassroots Approach to Volunteer Voices</title></titleInfo></relatedItem><language><languageTerm type="code">eng</languageTerm></language><accessCondition type="use and reproduction" xlink:href="http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/">Copyright Undetermined</accessCondition><location><url access="object in context" usage="primary display">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A11850</url><url access="preview">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A11850/datastream/TN/view</url></location></mods>