<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
      xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
      version="3.5"
      xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd">
   <titleInfo>
      <title>Nurses and their residence hall at the Mountain Branch of the National Home for Disabled Volunteer Soliders</title>
   </titleInfo>
   <typeOfResource>still image</typeOfResource>
   <genre authority="dct">still image</genre>
   <genre>black-and-white photographs</genre>
   <subject>
      <topic>Nurses.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Photographs.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Disabled veterans.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <geographic>Johnson City (Tenn.)</geographic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Disabled American Veterans -- Dept. Of Tennessee.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Wars and Military.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Women.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Health and Medicine.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <geographic>The Emergence of Modern America (1890-1930).</geographic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <geographic>Tennessee -- Washington County.</geographic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>National Home for Disabled Volunteer Soldiers.</topic>
   </subject>
   <note>National Homes for Disabled Volunteer Soldiers were created at the turn of the century for Civil War veterans, at the request of Abraham Lincoln. The Mountain Branch of the National Home for Disabled Volunteer Soliders was requested by Tennessee Congressman Walter P. Brownlow, and his bill passed unanimously in 1900. It was occupied in 1903 and was completed in 1910. The compound contained barracks for 2500 men, in addition to a 4 ward infirmary and homes for the surgeons and officers. The Mountain Branch in Johnson City, Tennessee became a tourist attraction, and hotels were built nearby to house visitors to the zoo and Home. The Home was not designed for permanent care or as a hospital, but for care of minor injuries. The officer veterans were expected to work during their stay according to their abilities. The nurses in the photo are listed: Miss Brown, Miss Jenner, Miss Elsie Finger, Miss Arnold, Miss Beeghler, Miss Wright; Miss Baker, Miss Redd, Miss Brown, Mrs. Lewis, Miss McFadden, Miss Arnold; Mrs. Smith, Miss Johansen, Miss Hider, Miss Ida Finger, Miss Moyer, Miss Richardson; Miss Baggerly, Miss Comstock, Miss Van Colen, Miss Clara Finger, Miss Singula, Mrs. Bowman; Miss Blocher</note>
   <note>The University of Tennessee Libraries (Knoxville, Tennessee) is the digital publisher.</note>
   <identifier type="local">TU:DLC:Filename:0061_000050_000203_0000</identifier>
   <relatedItem>
      <titleInfo>
         <title>Digital Collection: The Growth of Democracy in Tennessee: A Grassroots Approach to Volunteer Voices</title>
      </titleInfo>
   </relatedItem>
   <language>
      <languageTerm type="code">eng</languageTerm>
   </language>
   <accessCondition type="use and reproduction"
                    xlink:href="http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/">Copyright Undetermined</accessCondition>
   <location>
      <url access="object in context" usage="primary display">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A11912</url>
      <url access="preview">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A11912/datastream/TN/view</url>
   </location>
   <recordInfo>
      <recordContentSource>University of Tennessee, Knoxville. Libraries</recordContentSource>
      <languageOfCataloging>
         <languageTerm authority="iso639-2b" type="code">eng</languageTerm>
      </languageOfCataloging>
      <recordOrigin>Created and edited in general conformance to MODS Guidelines (Version 3.5).</recordOrigin>
   </recordInfo>
</mods>