<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="3.5" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd"><titleInfo><title>Proclamation by the Governor of Tennessee to Provide for Local Defense</title></titleInfo><typeOfResource>text</typeOfResource><genre authority="dct">text</genre><genre>handbill</genre><subject><geographic>Tennessee -- History -- Civil War, 1860-1865.</geographic></subject><subject><topic>Confederate States of America -- Army.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Harris, Isham G. (Isham Green), 1818-1897</topic></subject><subject><topic>Debate over slavery, the Secession Crisis, and the Civil War: Tennessee as a uniquely divided border state .</topic></subject><subject><topic>Wars and Military.</topic></subject><subject><geographic>Civil War and Reconstruction (1850-1877).</geographic></subject><subject><geographic>Tennessee -- Franklin County.</geographic></subject><note>This handbill contains a proclamation by Governor Isham G. Harris to raise six thousand troops for a six-month term to provide for local defense. These troops must be composed of men between the ages of forty and fifty-five, and will not be ordered outside the boundaries of the state. If the force is not raised by August 1st, a draft will be use to provide enough men. After outlining the organizational details, Harris writes to inspire the men of Tennessee to stand and fight to protect their families, property, liberty and national independence from predatory bands of marauders. He appeals to their patriotism and reputation as citizens of the "Volunteer State" to rise up and resist the invaders.</note><note>The University of Tennessee Libraries (Knoxville, Tennessee) is the digital publisher.</note><identifier type="local">TU:DLC:Filename:0015_000057_000208_0000</identifier><relatedItem><titleInfo><title>Digital Collection: The Growth of Democracy in Tennessee: A Grassroots Approach to Volunteer Voices</title></titleInfo></relatedItem><language><languageTerm type="code">eng</languageTerm></language><accessCondition type="use and reproduction" xlink:href="http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/">Copyright Undetermined</accessCondition><location><url access="object in context" usage="primary display">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A15601</url><url access="preview">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A15601/datastream/TN/view</url></location></mods>