<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="3.5" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd"><titleInfo><title>Giles County Court House, Pulaski, Tenn. - 2655</title></titleInfo><typeOfResource>still image</typeOfResource><genre authority="dct">still image</genre><genre>postcards</genre><subject><topic>Courthouses Tennessee.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Postcards.</topic></subject><subject><geographic>Giles County (Tenn.) -- Buildings, Structures, Etc.</geographic></subject><subject><topic>Architecture.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Government and Politics.</topic></subject><subject><geographic>Postwar United States (1945-1970).</geographic></subject><subject><geographic>Tennessee -- Giles County.</geographic></subject><subject><geographic>Pulaski, Tennessee.</geographic></subject><subject><topic>Giles County Courthouse.</topic></subject><note>2 tifs. A postcard of the Giles County Courthouse in Pulaski, Tennessee. The black and white photograph of the building shows people sitting on the stairs and standing in front of the building's entrance arch, which is designed as a temple front. The architectural style of the building is renaissance revival or Beaux-arts style and the courthouse features a colonnaded clock tower atop the building. The entrance is framed with corinthian columns, and the facades of the building are brick arches that frame square windows. The first courthouse was built in 1811, and due to fire the building had to be reconstructed three times. The courthouse built in 1859 by the George Moore and Sons company cost nearly $30,000 to complete. It stood through the American Civil War, but suffered much damage. The courthouse was re-built in 1908 at a cost of $133,000. The building was added to the national register of historical places in 1983. The verso has no message, but lists the publisher as Loyd Drug Co., Pulaski, Tenn. and the Dexter Press, Pearl River, N.Y.</note><note>The University of Tennessee Libraries (Knoxville, Tennessee) is the digital publisher.</note><identifier type="local">TU:DLC:Filename:0096_000050_000208_0000</identifier><relatedItem><titleInfo><title>Digital Collection: The Growth of Democracy in Tennessee: A Grassroots Approach to Volunteer Voices</title></titleInfo></relatedItem><language><languageTerm type="code">eng</languageTerm></language><accessCondition type="use and reproduction" xlink:href="http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/">Copyright Undetermined</accessCondition><location><url access="object in context" usage="primary display">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A12137</url><url access="preview">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A12137/datastream/TN/view</url></location></mods>