<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="3.5" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd"><titleInfo><title>Annie Mae Hoover and related items</title></titleInfo><typeOfResource>still image</typeOfResource><genre authority="dct">still image</genre><genre>three dimensional object</genre><genre authority="dct">collection</genre><subject><topic>American National Red Cross.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Women's Army Corps (U.S.)</topic></subject><subject><topic>Badges.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Women.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Wars and Military.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Health and Medicine.</topic></subject><subject><geographic>The Great Depression and World War II (1929-1945).</geographic></subject><subject><geographic>Tennessee -- Bedford County.</geographic></subject><subject><topic>Photographs.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Hoover, Annie May.</topic></subject><note>3 tifs. A photograph of Annie May Hoover, her American Red Cross card, and two badges from the Women's Army Corps. Hoover served with the WAC - Women's Army Corps in WWII, and later worked with Red Cross. The WAC was an auxiliary unit to the Army, begun in 1942, and around 150,000 women served in the WAC and its predecessor. The WAC were the first women to serve in the army other than nurses, and were engaged in international battles as well as serving stateside. The first badge is a brown parallelogram with an eagle inside a circle embroidered on it in goldenrod ink. The second badge is a blue oval containing an embroidered geometric design. The card for the Red Cross was given in 1949 in recognition of Hoover's completion of the Advanced American National Red Cross course and that she would be able to aid the injured in Shelbyville. The card reads "The American National Red Cross Certifies That Annie May Hoover has completed the Advanced course of instruction in First Aid to the injured at Shelbyville, Tennessee. February 4, 1949. Alfred W. Caueenelt Administrator, First Aid, Water Safety and Accident Prevention." The black and white photograph of Annie Mae Hoover shows her as a young woman, with her hair pinned back, wearing a sailor style shirt.</note><note>The University of Tennessee Libraries (Knoxville, Tennessee) is the digital publisher.</note><identifier type="local">TU:DLC:Filename:0081_000051_000208_0000</identifier><relatedItem><titleInfo><title>Digital Collection: The Growth of Democracy in Tennessee: A Grassroots Approach to Volunteer Voices</title></titleInfo></relatedItem><language><languageTerm type="code">eng</languageTerm></language><accessCondition type="use and reproduction" xlink:href="http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/">Copyright Undetermined</accessCondition><location><url access="object in context" usage="primary display">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A12079</url><url access="preview">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A12079/datastream/TN/view</url></location></mods>