<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="3.5" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd"><titleInfo><title>The Robert Jones School, Lynnville, Tenn.</title></titleInfo><typeOfResource>still image</typeOfResource><genre authority="dct">still image</genre><genre>postcards</genre><subject><topic>Schools Public relations.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Postcards.</topic></subject><subject><geographic>Giles County (Tenn.)</geographic></subject><subject><topic>Education.</topic></subject><subject><geographic>The Great Depression and World War II (1929-1945).</geographic></subject><subject><geographic>Tennessee -- Giles County.</geographic></subject><subject><geographic>Lynnville, Tennessee.</geographic></subject><subject><topic>Robert Jones School.</topic></subject><note>2 tifs. A postcard of the Robert Jones School in Giles County, Tennessee. The photograph depicts a large square brick building with a central exterior stair below arched windows. The school is surrounded by a line of trees. To the right of the image the text "The Robert Jones School, Lynnville, Tenn." is written. The verso has the text printed "The Robert Jones School Lynnville, Giles County, Tenn. Founded in 1900 by Robert Brevard Jones. Buildings and Equipment, $25,000. Productive Endowment $25,000. Thorough preparation for Classic and Scientific Courses in college. Scientific Agriculture for the farmer's son. Burkholder and Dozier, Principals." The inscription reads, "Hello Vada How are you? Darling. Where did you see [unknown] don't you think he is the stuff." It was written to Miss Vada Spurlook, Gainesboro, Tennessee, and mailed on a green one cent Benjamin Franklin (in profile) stamp. Robert B. Jones school was founded in 1900 as a day school, but A.C. Burkholder and Howard Dozier added buildings for borders and ruined the finances of the school. The school was forced to merge with the Lynnville Academy, and later became the property for a public high school.</note><note>The University of Tennessee Libraries (Knoxville, Tennessee) is the digital publisher.</note><identifier type="local">TU:DLC:Filename:0096_000050_000225_0000</identifier><relatedItem><titleInfo><title>Digital Collection: The Growth of Democracy in Tennessee: A Grassroots Approach to Volunteer Voices</title></titleInfo></relatedItem><language><languageTerm type="code">eng</languageTerm></language><accessCondition type="use and reproduction" xlink:href="http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/">Copyright Undetermined</accessCondition><location><url access="object in context" usage="primary display">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A12164</url><url access="preview">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A12164/datastream/TN/view</url></location></mods>