<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="3.5" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd"><titleInfo><title>"Sunday afternoon group" photographs</title></titleInfo><typeOfResource>still image</typeOfResource><genre authority="dct">still image</genre><genre>black-and-white photographs</genre><subject><topic>African American youth.</topic></subject><subject><topic>African American youth Social life and customs.</topic></subject><subject><topic>African Americans -- Tennessee Knoxville History Pictorial works.</topic></subject><subject><geographic>Knoxville (Tenn.) -- Social Life And Customs</geographic></subject><subject><topic>African-Americans.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Popular Culture and Folklife.</topic></subject><subject><geographic>The Emergence of Modern America (1890-1930).</geographic></subject><subject><geographic>Tennessee -- Knox County.</geographic></subject><subject><topic>Photographs.</topic></subject><subject><topic>"Sunday Afternoon Group".</topic></subject><note>2 tifs. Two photographs of African American young adults, who called themselves the "Sunday afternoon group." The first photograph depicts the seven females of the group standing in front of the six males in the group, who sit atop a stone wall in front of a house. The women wear corset-style long dresses and large hats while the men wear suits and bowler hats. The second image depicts the group with the females on top of the wall, seated, while the males stand below them and look up at the women. These pictures were taken at a house on Cansler Street in Knoxville, Tennessee. The street was later renamed McGhee Street. On the back of the first photograph, the individuals are identified as follows: L-R, James Beck, William Brooks, Fritz Cansler, Dr. Charles Davis, and the last two individuals are unidentified. The women in the lower row are identified as: Myrtle Brook McGowan, "Hoss", unidentified, Mrs. Ida Woods, Mrs. Fritz Cansler (Porter), unidentified and Dolly Warren Baskerville.</note><note>The University of Tennessee Libraries (Knoxville, Tennessee) is the digital publisher.</note><identifier type="local">TU:DLC:Filename:0073_000050_000244_0000</identifier><relatedItem><titleInfo><title>Digital Collection: The Growth of Democracy in Tennessee: A Grassroots Approach to Volunteer Voices</title></titleInfo></relatedItem><language><languageTerm type="code">eng</languageTerm></language><accessCondition type="use and reproduction" xlink:href="http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/">Copyright Undetermined</accessCondition><location><url access="object in context" usage="primary display">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A12069</url><url access="preview">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A12069/datastream/TN/view</url></location></mods>