<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="3.5" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd"><titleInfo><title>American Legion and the National Sanatorium in Mountain Home, Tenneessee</title></titleInfo><typeOfResource>still image</typeOfResource><genre authority="dct">still image</genre><typeOfResource>text</typeOfResource><genre authority="dct">text</genre><genre>picture</genre><subject><topic>American Legion. Tennessee.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Veterans -- Tennessee -- Johnson City.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Sanatoriums -- Tennessee, East.</topic></subject><subject><geographic>Mountain Home (Tenn.)</geographic></subject><subject><topic>National Home for Disabled Volunteer Soldiers. Mountain Branch.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Mountain Home VA Medical Center (Johnson City, Tenn.)</topic></subject><subject><topic>Soldier's homes.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Veteran's organizations.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Wars and Military.</topic></subject><subject><geographic>The Emergence of Modern America (1890-1930).</geographic></subject><subject><geographic>Tennessee -- Washington County.</geographic></subject><subject><topic>Soldiers' homes -- Tennessee -- Johnson City.</topic></subject><note>The first image in this series is a welcoming card with a sketch of two men shaking two hands. The card reads, "The Lester Harris Post of the American Legion welcomes you buddie." The second image is of Lester Harris and gives vital information on Mr. Harris, for whom this post of the American Legion was named. The card reads: "Dedicated to the memory of Lester Harris; Born Orchard Place; Johnson City, Tennessee, December 31st 1893; Wounded Compeigne, France, July 5th, 1918; Died Catency, France, July 9, 1918." The third image is a group portrait of the leaders of National Sanatorium in Tennessee. The officers were: Vice Commander, Lewis E. Shaver; Adjutant, F.J. Lindenthal; Treasurer, H.Y. Anderson; Sergeant-At-Arms, Albert Alder. The leaders of the committees were: Publicity, Quin E. Donathan; Membership, Mack Lee; Compensation, R. Bernsteine. The last image is a photograph of an American Legion gathering in the theater located on the premises of National Sanatorium at Mountain Home, Tennessee. The National Sanatorium is now known as the Moutain Home VA Medical Center or the James H. Quillen VA Medical Center.</note><note>The University of Tennessee Libraries (Knoxville, Tennessee) is the digital publisher.</note><identifier type="local">TU:DLC:Filename:0061_000050_000202_0000</identifier><relatedItem><titleInfo><title>Digital Collection: The Growth of Democracy in Tennessee: A Grassroots Approach to Volunteer Voices</title></titleInfo></relatedItem><language><languageTerm type="code">eng</languageTerm></language><accessCondition type="use and reproduction" xlink:href="http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/">Copyright Undetermined</accessCondition><location><url access="object in context" usage="primary display">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A11909</url><url access="preview">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A11909/datastream/TN/view</url></location></mods>