<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="3.5" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd"><titleInfo><title>Sam Davis Tomb, Pulaski, Tenn. - SPC-224-C</title></titleInfo><typeOfResource>still image</typeOfResource><genre authority="dct">still image</genre><genre>postcards</genre><subject><topic>Confederate States of America History.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Monuments and memorials.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Wars and Military.</topic></subject><subject><geographic>Postwar United States (1945-1970).</geographic></subject><subject><geographic>Tennessee -- Rutherford County.</geographic></subject><subject><topic>Postcards.</topic></subject><subject><geographic>Smyrna, Tennessee.</geographic></subject><subject><topic>Davis, Sam.</topic></subject><note>2 tifs. A postcard of the tomb of Sam Davis at his home in Smyrna, Tennessee. The white marble tomb is in the style of a Greek temple with a semi-circular colonnade around the front door with Sam Davis Memorial engraved above. The building features two bronze plaques with information about Davis as well. Davis was known as the "boy hero of the Confederacy," and was a private in the first Tennessee Volunteer infantry in 1861, and was captured in 1863 in possession of Union battle plans. Upon his capture he was attributed with the statement "If I had a thousand lives to live, I would give them all, rather than betray a friend or my country." The home was preserved at the time of his death and includes the original woodwork and family pieces. The home and grounds were purchased by the state of Tennessee in 1927 and opened for tours in 1930. In addition to his home serving as a monument to Davis, two statues were erected in his honor one in Pulaski, Tennessee and one at the state capitol in Nashville, Tennessee. The verso is blank but lists the Southern Post Card Co., Box 306, Goodlettsville, Tenn. 37072. It describes the monument: "Sam Davis Tomb--Pulaski, Tenn. Doomed by Federals in Civil War because he would not betray a trust. "If I had a thousand live, I'd give them all rather than betray a friend."</note><note>The University of Tennessee Libraries (Knoxville, Tennessee) is the digital publisher.</note><identifier type="local">TU:DLC:Filename:0096_000050_000215_0000</identifier><relatedItem><titleInfo><title>Digital Collection: The Growth of Democracy in Tennessee: A Grassroots Approach to Volunteer Voices</title></titleInfo></relatedItem><language><languageTerm type="code">eng</languageTerm></language><accessCondition type="use and reproduction" xlink:href="http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/">Copyright Undetermined</accessCondition><location><url access="object in context" usage="primary display">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A12152</url><url access="preview">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A12152/datastream/TN/view</url></location></mods>