<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
      xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
      version="3.5"
      xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd">
   <titleInfo>
      <title>Remarks by the President of Fisk University, The Flag</title>
   </titleInfo>
   <typeOfResource>text</typeOfResource>
   <genre authority="dct">text</genre>
   <genre>brochures</genre>
   <subject>
      <topic>Fisk University.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Flag raising and lowering\t.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Popular Culture and Folklife.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Education.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Civil and Human Rights.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <geographic>The Emergence of Modern America (1890-1930).</geographic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <geographic>Tennessee -- Davidson County.</geographic>
   </subject>
   <note>3 tifs. A three page brochure issued at an event where Fisk college raised the flag over Jubilee Hall on September 22, 1915. The flag raising and speech was to "mark the opening of the New Year and the Anniversary of the Preliminary Announcement by Lincoln of the Freeing of the Slave, September 22, 1862." The page was signed by Dr. F.A. Mc Kenzie. The first page features a black and white image of one of the college`s buildings flying a flag and featuring a tall tree in front. The second page is in praise of the flag and its symbolism, with two images of the college. The page reads in part, "The Flag represents in its aspects of patriotism, of national devotion, two great ideas, two great facts. The first great idea, the first great fact, is that of Obedience. . . . The second great idea, the second great fact, is that of Perfection. . . . When we are true to our flag we are true to that kingdom whose law is, Be ye therefore perfect." The third page text aligns Lincoln with the flag, stating "The flag of Lincoln is the flag of the South, and the flag of the North, the flag of the white and the flag of the black. It is the flag under whose folds no slave can breathe. . . . The flag and freedom and education are inseparable."</note>
   <note>The University of Tennessee Libraries (Knoxville, Tennessee) is the digital publisher.</note>
   <identifier type="local">TU:DLC:Filename:0093_000050_000201_0000</identifier>
   <relatedItem>
      <titleInfo>
         <title>Digital Collection: The Growth of Democracy in Tennessee: A Grassroots Approach to Volunteer Voices</title>
      </titleInfo>
   </relatedItem>
   <language>
      <languageTerm type="code">eng</languageTerm>
   </language>
   <accessCondition type="use and reproduction"
                    xlink:href="http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/">Copyright Undetermined</accessCondition>
   <location>
      <url access="object in context" usage="primary display">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A9939</url>
      <url access="preview">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A9939/datastream/TN/view</url>
   </location>
   <recordInfo>
      <recordContentSource>University of Tennessee, Knoxville. Libraries</recordContentSource>
      <languageOfCataloging>
         <languageTerm authority="iso639-2b" type="code">eng</languageTerm>
      </languageOfCataloging>
      <recordOrigin>Created and edited in general conformance to MODS Guidelines (Version 3.5).</recordOrigin>
   </recordInfo>
</mods>