<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="3.5" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd"><titleInfo><title>Photographs from Maryville Polytechnic School in Tennessee</title></titleInfo><typeOfResource>still image</typeOfResource><genre authority="dct">still image</genre><typeOfResource>text</typeOfResource><genre authority="dct">text</genre><genre>black-and-white photographs</genre><subject><topic>School photographs.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Football.</topic></subject><subject><geographic>Maryville (Tenn.) -- History -- Pictorial Works</geographic></subject><subject><geographic>Maryville (Tenn.) -- Buildings, Structures, Etc. -- Pictorial Works</geographic></subject><subject><topic>Education.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Sports and Recreation.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Architecture.</topic></subject><subject><geographic>The Emergence of Modern America (1890-1930).</geographic></subject><subject><geographic>Tennessee -- Blount County.</geographic></subject><subject><topic>Photographs.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Maryville Polytechnic School.</topic></subject><note>6 tifs. A collection of images related to the Maryville Polytechnic School, which was a part of the Maryville School system, started in 1900. First image: A photograph of the main building of the Maryville Polytechnic School. The school was demolished in the late 1930s and the site was used for the current Maryville High School. The building is in the Beaux-Arts style, with a central bell tower. Second: A portrait of the Maryville Polytechnic Football Squad for 1917, which appears to have been printed for circulation. The team of eighteen are seated with their arms crossed, wearing their uniforms which displayed their number on the chest. The caption below the image reads "These boys won the East Tennessee Championship last year. They played nine games, lost one, tied one, and won seven, Polytechnic made 161 points, their opponents made 25 points. The Basket Ball Team of Polytechnic tied with Knoxville High School for the East Tennessee Championship in Basket Ball, this year. They played ten games and won nine of them. Polytechnic points 352, opponents points 171. The Girls Basket Ball Team of Polytechnic also lost only one game." Third: A photograph of six male and female students sitting at a long desk and practicing typing skills. The students have cloth swags covering their shoulders that prevented them from seeing the keys as they typed. The students are most likely in their teens. Fourth: Back of the image reading "Aunt Emma's Davis typing class at Polytechnic School. Note the cloth swags covering the typewriters so they coudl not see the keys." Fifth: Eighteen members of the Maryville Polytechnic School band stand staggered in the school's front lawn. The band ranged in age from around ten to adult, and included two female players. The band uniform was a dark blazer and tie with white pants for men and white outfits for women. Sixth: Back of the image reading "Maryville Polytechnic School Band/ Leader: Bill Jo Henry center/ Left of Prof. Henry: Martha Henry with trumpet/ Right--Mattie Ledford."</note><note>The University of Tennessee Libraries (Knoxville, Tennessee) is the digital publisher.</note><identifier type="local">TU:DLC:Filename:0020_000050_000224_0000</identifier><relatedItem><titleInfo><title>Digital Collection: The Growth of Democracy in Tennessee: A Grassroots Approach to Volunteer Voices</title></titleInfo></relatedItem><language><languageTerm type="code">eng</languageTerm></language><accessCondition type="use and reproduction" xlink:href="http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/">Copyright Undetermined</accessCondition><location><url access="object in context" usage="primary display">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A11634</url><url access="preview">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A11634/datastream/TN/view</url></location></mods>