<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
      xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
      version="3.5"
      xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd">
   <titleInfo>
      <title>Giles County Court House</title>
   </titleInfo>
   <typeOfResource>still image</typeOfResource>
   <genre authority="dct">still image</genre>
   <genre>postcards</genre>
   <subject>
      <topic>Courthouses Tennessee.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Postcards.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <geographic>Giles County (Tenn.) -- Buildings, Structures, Etc.</geographic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Architecture.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Government and Politics.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <geographic>The Great Depression and World War II (1929-1945).</geographic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <geographic>Tennessee -- Giles County.</geographic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <geographic>Pulaski, Tennessee.</geographic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Giles County Courthouse.</topic>
   </subject>
   <note>2 tifs. A postcard featuring the Pulaski, Tennessee courthouse and the neighboring streets, lined with cars. The courthouse building features a colonnaded clock tower atop a four-sided temple style building, in the Beaux Arts design. The first courthouse was built in 1811, and due to fire the building had to be reconstructed three times. The courthouse built in 1859 by the George Moore and Sons company cost nearly $30,000 to complete. It stood through the American Civil War, but suffered much damage. The building was reconstructed in 1908 at a cost of $133, 000. The courthouse was added to the national register of historical places in 1983. The verso reads "Dear Bill: Here we are again at Pulaski, in the same cabins and every thing. You should of been here with us. We had the most marvelous supper. How's everything with you? Are maneuvers fun. We are still keeping up our physical training. We picked cotton this afternoon in Ala, and Mr. Johnson too our pictures. Love, Rosa." Sent to Pvt. Paul Wm. Moss 35893599 Co. C. 17th Bn 5 Regt. IR.TC. Fort McClellan, Ala U.S. Army. The time stamp reads Nashville, Tenn. Nov. 29 2:30 PM 1943. The stamp is a green one cent stamp featuring a bust of George Washington. It was stamped "Buy War Savings Bond and Stamps."</note>
   <note>The University of Tennessee Libraries (Knoxville, Tennessee) is the digital publisher.</note>
   <identifier type="local">TU:DLC:Filename:0096_000050_000210_0000</identifier>
   <relatedItem>
      <titleInfo>
         <title>Digital Collection: The Growth of Democracy in Tennessee: A Grassroots Approach to Volunteer Voices</title>
      </titleInfo>
   </relatedItem>
   <language>
      <languageTerm type="code">eng</languageTerm>
   </language>
   <accessCondition type="use and reproduction"
                    xlink:href="http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/">Copyright Undetermined</accessCondition>
   <location>
      <url access="object in context" usage="primary display">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A12143</url>
      <url access="preview">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A12143/datastream/TN/view</url>
   </location>
   <recordInfo>
      <recordContentSource>University of Tennessee, Knoxville. Libraries</recordContentSource>
      <languageOfCataloging>
         <languageTerm authority="iso639-2b" type="code">eng</languageTerm>
      </languageOfCataloging>
      <recordOrigin>Created and edited in general conformance to MODS Guidelines (Version 3.5).</recordOrigin>
   </recordInfo>
</mods>