<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="3.5" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd"><titleInfo><title>Report of West Point Military Academy</title></titleInfo><typeOfResource>text</typeOfResource><genre authority="dct">text</genre><genre>manuscripts</genre><subject><topic>Military education -- New York (State) -- West Point</topic></subject><subject><topic>United States Military Academy -- Study and teaching (Higher) -- New York</topic></subject><subject><topic>Eaton, John, 1829-1906.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Education.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Wars and Military.</topic></subject><subject><geographic>Civil War and Reconstruction (1850-1877).</geographic></subject><note>This is a report of findings of the board making a study of the Military Academy. The concerns are the quality of instruction, and the use of assistant professors and the examinations are found to be especially beneficial. The board recommends pay increases for assistant professors. Curriculum evaluation criticizes too great an emphasis place upon some courses and suggests introduction of new courses. The board recommends that mastery of English be given more emphasis, that courses in the scientific method, geography, U.S. History and hygiene be added and that examinations be used. The board suggests ways of of increasing the school`s geological collection. The board also compares West Point to the French Military Academy and urges adoption of some of their standards, including stringent entrance requirements. The board sets forth their ideas on the West Point graduate`s place in society and recommends a broader education at the Academy. The report is written mostly in John Eaton`s handwriting.</note><note>The University of Tennessee Libraries (Knoxville, Tennessee) is the digital publisher.</note><identifier type="local">TU:DLC:Filename:0012_000053_000220_0000</identifier><relatedItem><titleInfo><title>Digital Collection: The Growth of Democracy in Tennessee: A Grassroots Approach to Volunteer Voices</title></titleInfo></relatedItem><language><languageTerm type="code">eng</languageTerm></language><accessCondition type="use and reproduction" xlink:href="http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/">Copyright Undetermined</accessCondition><location><url access="object in context" usage="primary display">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A4145</url><url access="preview">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A4145/datastream/TN/view</url></location></mods>