<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
      xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
      version="3.5"
      xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd">
   <titleInfo>
      <title>Singing Campaign for Ten Thousand Pounds, or Jubilee Singers in Great Britain</title>
   </titleInfo>
   <typeOfResource>text</typeOfResource>
   <genre authority="dct">text</genre>
   <typeOfResource>still image</typeOfResource>
   <genre authority="dct">still image</genre>
   <genre>books</genre>
   <subject>
      <topic>Educational fund raising.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Fund raising Periodicals.\t.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>African-Americans.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Education.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Arts and Literature.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <geographic>Expansion and Reform (1801-1861).</geographic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <geographic>Tennessee -- Davidson County.</geographic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Jubilee Singers of Fisk University.</topic>
   </subject>
   <note>7 tifs. The front pages and table of contents of a book printed in Great Britain during the tour by the Jubilee Singers. The Jubilee Singers were created when George White, professor of music, decide to take a nine-member choral ensemble on the road to generate funds for the University. The group left on October 6, 1871, which is now a holiday for the University. In 1872 they sang at the World Peace festival in Boston and for President Ulysses S. Grant. In 1873 eleven members of the group toured Europe and generated funds for the school`s first permanent building, Jubilee Hall. The images are numbered with their contents. 1: The cover. Reading: "The Singing Campaign for Ten Thousand Pounds or the Jubilee Singers in Great Britain." The cover is dark blue with gold text and features a harp and scroll symbol in the center. 2: An illustration of the Jubilee Singers. The names read: E. Watkins. I.P. Dickerson. B.M. Holmes. T. Rutling. Georgie Gordon. Mabel Lewis. Maggie Porter. Jennie Jackson. Ella Sheppard. Julia Jackson. Minnie Tate. 3: The Jubilee Singers, and their Campaign for Twenty Thousand Dollars. By the Rev. G.D. Pike B.A., District Secretary of the American Missionary Association. Twenty-seventh Thousand. London. Hodder and Stoughton. Boston, U.S.A: Lee and Shepard. 1874. 4: Advertisement to the English Edition. The visit of the Jubilee Singers to England has necessitated a new Edition of this work, the American Edition of which has attained a circulation of nearly ten thousand copies in three months. The book contains a history of the first singing tour, but a year has since elapsed, during which, such increasing success has attended the efforts of the Singers, that they have been encouraged to appeal to the English public for aid in the accomplishment of their mission. The Jubilee Hall of Fisk University (a cut of which forms the frontispiece) is already partly erected, and funds are now required to complete the building. 27, Paternoster Row, May, 1873. 5: Preface. The following pages were prepared at intervals during the summer vacation, for the purpose of answering numerous questions about the Jubilee Singers. The statements respecting the illiteracy of the South, the campaign for Twenty Thousand Dollars, the Fisk University, and the American Missionary Association, are reliable. The personal histories were gathered chiefly by a former teacher of Fisk University, who has rendered me great service in preparing this volume for the press in season for our coming campaign for the further endowment of that institution. That the reader may be inspired with a noble enthusiasm to repair the damages done by Slavery, and to restore fourfold to a race that has been wronged, is the most earnest wish of the author. G.D.P. Acton, October 1, 1872. 6: Contents. Chapter I. The American Missionary Association. --Collecting Agents. --The New Era. 9.; Chapter II. Value of Institutions. --Fisk University. 25.; Chapter III. Teachers for Freedmen. --George L. White. 39; Chapter IV. Personal History of the Jubilee Singers. 49.; Chaper V. Nashville to Oberlin. 77.; Chapter VI. Oberlin to New York. 98. 7: Contents page 8: Chapter VII. Turning Tide--At New York. 110.; Chapter VII. From Hartford to Boston. 125.; Chapter IX. Boston to Nashville. 142.</note>
   <note>The University of Tennessee Libraries (Knoxville, Tennessee) is the digital publisher.</note>
   <identifier type="local">TU:DLC:Filename:0093_000050_000200_0000</identifier>
   <relatedItem>
      <titleInfo>
         <title>Digital Collection: The Growth of Democracy in Tennessee: A Grassroots Approach to Volunteer Voices</title>
      </titleInfo>
   </relatedItem>
   <language>
      <languageTerm type="code">eng</languageTerm>
   </language>
   <accessCondition type="use and reproduction"
                    xlink:href="http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/">Copyright Undetermined</accessCondition>
   <location>
      <url access="object in context" usage="primary display">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A9943</url>
      <url access="preview">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A9943/datastream/TN/view</url>
   </location>
   <recordInfo>
      <recordContentSource>University of Tennessee, Knoxville. Libraries</recordContentSource>
      <languageOfCataloging>
         <languageTerm authority="iso639-2b" type="code">eng</languageTerm>
      </languageOfCataloging>
      <recordOrigin>Created and edited in general conformance to MODS Guidelines (Version 3.5).</recordOrigin>
   </recordInfo>
</mods>