<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
      xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
      version="3.5"
      xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd">
   <titleInfo>
      <title>Service of Song, Slave Hymns [amp] Melodies, The Jubilee Singers</title>
   </titleInfo>
   <typeOfResource>text</typeOfResource>
   <genre authority="dct">text</genre>
   <genre>souvenir programs</genre>
   <subject>
      <topic>Fisk University. Jubilee Singers.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Concerts.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Concert programs.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>African-Americans.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Music and Performing Arts.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Education.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <geographic>Civil War and Reconstruction (1850-1877).</geographic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <geographic>Tennessee -- Davidson County.</geographic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Fisk University Jubilee Singers.</topic>
   </subject>
   <note>4 tifs. A program for a concert by the Jubilee Singers on February 12, 1874 held at the Exchange Opera House in Wolverhampton, England under patronage of the mayor, W.H. Jones, various gentlemen and ministers. The concert was billed as a "Service of Song consisting of slave hymns [amp] melodies." The program lists the ticket prices, Rev. G.D. Pike as the District Secretary of the American Missionary Association, and George White as the treasurer of Fisk University. On the pages that follow there is information about the tour and how the group is seeking to earn 14,000 pounds to aid in building Fisk University, and testimonials from those who have heard the singers perform. The testimonials mention that some of the singers were previously slaves, and sing "wild slave songs" that are unlike any music Europeans have heard. The testimonials also conflate the singers` performance with supporting emancipation and restitution of former slaves. The final page of the program lists the chartered institutions of the American Missionary Association, including Fisk University. Additional programs for concerts in 1874 in Birmingham and Cambridge are also included in the collection, as well as a similar program for a concert in Germany in 1877.</note>
   <note>The University of Tennessee Libraries (Knoxville, Tennessee) is the digital publisher.</note>
   <identifier type="local">TU:DLC:Filename:0093_000050_000206_0000</identifier>
   <relatedItem>
      <titleInfo>
         <title>Digital Collection: The Growth of Democracy in Tennessee: A Grassroots Approach to Volunteer Voices</title>
      </titleInfo>
   </relatedItem>
   <language>
      <languageTerm type="code">eng</languageTerm>
   </language>
   <accessCondition type="use and reproduction"
                    xlink:href="http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/">Copyright Undetermined</accessCondition>
   <location>
      <url access="object in context" usage="primary display">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A9923</url>
      <url access="preview">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A9923/datastream/TN/view</url>
   </location>
   <recordInfo>
      <recordContentSource>University of Tennessee, Knoxville. Libraries</recordContentSource>
      <languageOfCataloging>
         <languageTerm authority="iso639-2b" type="code">eng</languageTerm>
      </languageOfCataloging>
      <recordOrigin>Created and edited in general conformance to MODS Guidelines (Version 3.5).</recordOrigin>
   </recordInfo>
</mods>