<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="3.5" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd"><titleInfo><title>Twenty-sixth Annual Meeting of the White Cross League of Fisk University</title></titleInfo><typeOfResource>text</typeOfResource><genre authority="dct">text</genre><genre>souvenir programs</genre><subject><topic>Fisk University.</topic></subject><subject><topic>White Cross League.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Souvenir programs.</topic></subject><subject><topic>African-Americans.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Education.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Religion.</topic></subject><subject><geographic>The Emergence of Modern America (1890-1930).</geographic></subject><subject><geographic>Tennessee -- Davidson County.</geographic></subject><subject><topic>Fisk University White Cross League.</topic></subject><note>4 tifs. A brochure for the White Cross League, a student organization at Fisk University, announcing their twenty-sixth annual meeting on April 18,1915 at the Fisk Memorial chapel at 3 p.m. The motto "My Strength is as the Strength of Ten Because my Heart is Pure" is printed at the bottom. The second page is the program of events, including songs, scripture readings, prayer, and an address by Dr. James I. Vance. It also lists the officers and executive committee. The third page provides a list of the active members and the White Cross Pledge, which is committed to respecting women and treating them as equals and "to use every possible way to fulfill the command, `Keep thyself pure.`" The final page is a poem titled "To-Day`s Demand," which reads like a prayer for men who have "strong minds, great hearts, true faith, and ready hands..." The White Cross league was an extracurricular club that was devoted to a religious purpose, while other extracurricular clubs at Fisk were literary or aimed at dramatics.</note><note>The University of Tennessee Libraries (Knoxville, Tennessee) is the digital publisher.</note><identifier type="local">TU:DLC:Filename:0093_000053_000203_0000</identifier><relatedItem><titleInfo><title>Digital Collection: The Growth of Democracy in Tennessee: A Grassroots Approach to Volunteer Voices</title></titleInfo></relatedItem><language><languageTerm type="code">eng</languageTerm></language><accessCondition type="use and reproduction" xlink:href="http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/">Copyright Undetermined</accessCondition><location><url access="object in context" usage="primary display">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A9905</url><url access="preview">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A9905/datastream/TN/view</url></location></mods>