<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="3.5" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd"><titleInfo><title>Proceedings with the Cherokees, Tellico Block House, December, 1794 [amp] January, 1795</title></titleInfo><typeOfResource>text</typeOfResource><genre authority="dct">text</genre><genre>treaties</genre><subject><topic>Cherokee Indians Treaties.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Cherokee Indians Government relations.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Blount, William, 1749-1800.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Native Americans.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Government and Politics.</topic></subject><subject><geographic>Revolution and the New Nation (1754-1820).</geographic></subject><subject><geographic>Tennessee -- Davidson County.</geographic></subject><subject><topic>Bloody Fellow, the.</topic></subject><note>A copy of the President`s Certificate respecting the Bounds of the Chickasaws Lands. Beginning Dec 28, 1794, a record of the minutes of treaty negotiations between Governor William Blount, Silas Dinsmoor, and John McKee and Agents to the Cherokees and several Cherokee leaders including the Bloody Fellow. The first page has a list of those present that day, starting with Blount. Blount first states that the negotiations are for a trade of prisoners and peace in the future, with the understanding that there has been many injuries on each side in the past. Blount urges the tribes to move to the Chatanuga mountain and join the Creek tribes. The talks the next few days center on prisoner trading. The Bloody Fellow states that he does not want to move and live with the Creek tribes, and urges Blount to accept a treaty brokered with Dinsmoor. In January the two speak to the posts erected around the Indian settlement which the settlers find comforting but the Indians find restrictive to hunting. Blount accused Bloody Fellow of stealing horses, and Bloody Fellow says if whites want to see their horses they should go to North Carolina. The next day Blount states that the treaties are settled but the Cherokee should help broker a peace with the Creeks whom the Cherokee are not in accord with. The talks discuss the relationship of Tennessee with the other tribes and the difficulties that arise from the tribes and whites sharing the land. They also discuss at length prisoners, and the desire for peace.</note><note>The University of Tennessee Libraries (Knoxville, Tennessee) is the digital publisher.</note><identifier type="local">TU:DLC:Filename:0017_000050_000219_0000</identifier><relatedItem><titleInfo><title>Digital Collection: The Growth of Democracy in Tennessee: A Grassroots Approach to Volunteer Voices</title></titleInfo></relatedItem><language><languageTerm type="code">eng</languageTerm></language><accessCondition type="use and reproduction" xlink:href="http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/">Copyright Undetermined</accessCondition><location><url access="object in context" usage="primary display">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A13490</url><url access="preview">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A13490/datastream/TN/view</url></location></mods>