<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
      xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
      version="3.5"
      xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd">
   <titleInfo>
      <title>Emerald-Hodgson Memorial Hospital, Sewanee, Tennessee</title>
   </titleInfo>
   <typeOfResource>still image</typeOfResource>
   <genre authority="dct">still image</genre>
   <genre>brochures</genre>
   <subject>
      <topic>Hospitals Tennessee History.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Fund raising Periodicals.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <geographic>Sewanee (Tenn.)</geographic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Health and Medicine.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <geographic>The Emergence of Modern America (1890-1930).</geographic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <geographic>Tennessee -- Franklin County.</geographic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Brochures.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Emerald-Hodgson Memorial Hospital.</topic>
   </subject>
   <note>5 tifs. A brochure for the Emerald-Hodgson Memorial Hospital in Sewanee, Tennessee. The brochure features images of the hospital and nearby residents and appears to have been produced in order to raise funds for the hospital. Emerald-Hodgson Memorial Hospital was founded in 1877, and still operated at the turn of the 21st century. The first image is of the front of the brochure and features at the top a photograph of three men precariously carrying an injured man over a makeshift wooden bridge. Below the men the text "Emerald-Hodgson Memorial Hospital. Sewannee Tennessee" is printed. The second image is a page of five photographs of mountain life. The first image, captioned "A Mountain Home" is a wooden house and picket fence with women standing just behind it. The second image, "Mountain Families," is of two women holding children with a young girl at their side standing by a man in crutches. The third image, "A Hospital Patient," on the bottom left is of a small girl sitting on a porch; the fourth his a man standing wearing a poncho titled "A contemporary," and the fifth is a family sitting around a fire, with the father holding a screaming baby, sharing the caption "Mountain Families." The third page contains images of the hospital, including an operating room a blank square reading "X-ray Department $2,500.00 needed to complete equipment," the obstetrical room and the out-patient clinic. All three images feature clean, tiled rooms with all-white equipment and high beds with white sheets. The outpatient clinic contains a chest of drawers containing medicines. The fourth page features the Children's Ward, the Chapel, the Nurses' Home and a photograph of the Staff group. The children's ward has an image of two white metal beds with white sheets; the chapel is simply a carved metal altar featuring candles and crosses; the Nurses' home is a square building made with a stone facade and hip roof; the staff group photograph is of seven women dressed in white tops and skirts with white hats in front of three men in suits standing on the front stair of the hospital. The final page is an exterior photograph of the hospital, which was a large structure with long windows above an entrance arch with stairs flanked by two smaller arches. Two cars sit out front of the hospital as well.</note>
   <note>The University of Tennessee Libraries (Knoxville, Tennessee) is the digital publisher.</note>
   <identifier type="local">TU:DLC:Filename:0087_000051_000200_0000</identifier>
   <relatedItem>
      <titleInfo>
         <title>Digital Collection: The Growth of Democracy in Tennessee: A Grassroots Approach to Volunteer Voices</title>
      </titleInfo>
   </relatedItem>
   <language>
      <languageTerm type="code">eng</languageTerm>
   </language>
   <accessCondition type="use and reproduction"
                    xlink:href="http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/">Copyright Undetermined</accessCondition>
   <location>
      <url access="object in context" usage="primary display">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A12131</url>
      <url access="preview">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A12131/datastream/TN/view</url>
   </location>
   <recordInfo>
      <recordContentSource>University of Tennessee, Knoxville. Libraries</recordContentSource>
      <languageOfCataloging>
         <languageTerm authority="iso639-2b" type="code">eng</languageTerm>
      </languageOfCataloging>
      <recordOrigin>Created and edited in general conformance to MODS Guidelines (Version 3.5).</recordOrigin>
   </recordInfo>
</mods>