<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
      xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
      version="3.5"
      xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd">
   <titleInfo>
      <title>The Child of the Regiment</title>
   </titleInfo>
   <genre>notated music</genre>
   <genre>sheet music</genre>
   <subject>
      <topic>Music and Performing Arts.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Women.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <geographic>Expansion and Reform (1801-1861).</geographic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Tennessee History.</topic>
   </subject>
   <note>The preface to this song is "During the occupation of the Tyrol by the French and after a skirmish between the hostile ranks, an infant child was found alone in their camp by the 11th Regiment of the Grand Army of Napoleon. And by that regiment she was fostered and beloved, and all were proud of the charming Vivandiere Maria, the name given to the child, upon the attainment of her 18th year was discovered to be the daughter of the Marchioness de Berkenfield, and by her moved to a sphere more consonant to the dignity of her birth. Still the affectionate girl found it impossible to shake off the attachment of her childhood, and being reproached by her mother with want of pride, defended herself in the words of this song, which is so exquisitely sung by the renowned Cantatrice, Jenny Lind, in the Opera of "La Fille Du Regiment," as to entitle it to be called the gem of the opera." This piece is included in a bound volume of sheet music once owned by Miss Nora Gardner of Tennessee.</note>
   <note>The University of Tennessee Libraries (Knoxville, Tennessee) is the digital publisher.</note>
   <identifier type="local">TU:DLC:Filename:0018_000054_000272_0000</identifier>
   <relatedItem>
      <titleInfo>
         <title>Digital Collection: The Growth of Democracy in Tennessee: A Grassroots Approach to Volunteer Voices</title>
      </titleInfo>
   </relatedItem>
   <accessCondition type="use and reproduction"
                    xlink:href="http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/">Copyright Undetermined</accessCondition>
   <location>
      <url access="object in context" usage="primary display">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A10588</url>
      <url access="preview">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A10588/datastream/TN/view</url>
   </location>
   <recordInfo>
      <recordContentSource>University of Tennessee, Knoxville. Libraries</recordContentSource>
      <languageOfCataloging>
         <languageTerm authority="iso639-2b" type="code">eng</languageTerm>
      </languageOfCataloging>
      <recordOrigin>Created and edited in general conformance to MODS Guidelines (Version 3.5).</recordOrigin>
   </recordInfo>
</mods>