<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
      xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
      version="3.5"
      xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd">
   <titleInfo>
      <title>Concert Program for Fisk Jubilee Singers of Nashville, Tenn. in Syracuse, N.Y.</title>
   </titleInfo>
   <typeOfResource>text</typeOfResource>
   <genre authority="dct">text</genre>
   <genre>souvenir programs</genre>
   <subject>
      <topic>Fisk University. Jubilee Singers.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Concerts.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Concert programs.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>African-Americans.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Music and Performing Arts.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Education.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <geographic>The Emergence of Modern America (1890-1930).</geographic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <geographic>Tennessee -- Davidson County.</geographic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Fisk University Jubilee Singers.</topic>
   </subject>
   <note>4 tifs. A program touting the Fisk University Jubilee Singers of Nashville, Tennessee as "Unsurpassed by Anything that has Ever Been Before the Public." The first page includes a photograph of the singers listing: Miss E. Bowman, Mr. G. E. Martin, John W. Work, A.M. conductor, Miss M.L. Grant, Mr. S.S. Carruthers, Miss I. M. Napier, Mr. A. E. Greenlaw, Mrs. Agnes M. Work, Chaperon, Rev. H. A, Merrill, Manager, Miss S. V. Hayes. The concert was to be held on December 11, at 8 p.m. in the Y.M.C.A. Hall in Syracuse, New York at a cost of 35 cents. The first page also includes a paragraph about the folk songs and the performance. The second page details the history, mission and recent press on the group. This group is the second incarnation of the Fisk University singers, which comprises nine singers, and their mission statement talks about the University and how the group is fundraising. The press letters includes testimonials about the group`s musical ability but also about their general demeanor. The third page is devoted to testimonials, mostly given by representatives from churches. The fourth page continues testimonials, but also includes the program consisting of two parts. The bottom of the pages lists Rev. H.A. Merrill as the manager and directs all letters to him at Fisk University. Handwritten at the bottom is the text "Encores were usually called for. Property of M.E. Sherrde."</note>
   <note>The University of Tennessee Libraries (Knoxville, Tennessee) is the digital publisher.</note>
   <identifier type="local">TU:DLC:Filename:0093_000050_000207_0000</identifier>
   <relatedItem>
      <titleInfo>
         <title>Digital Collection: The Growth of Democracy in Tennessee: A Grassroots Approach to Volunteer Voices</title>
      </titleInfo>
   </relatedItem>
   <language>
      <languageTerm type="code">eng</languageTerm>
   </language>
   <accessCondition type="use and reproduction"
                    xlink:href="http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/">Copyright Undetermined</accessCondition>
   <location>
      <url access="object in context" usage="primary display">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A9918</url>
      <url access="preview">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A9918/datastream/TN/view</url>
   </location>
   <recordInfo>
      <recordContentSource>University of Tennessee, Knoxville. Libraries</recordContentSource>
      <languageOfCataloging>
         <languageTerm authority="iso639-2b" type="code">eng</languageTerm>
      </languageOfCataloging>
      <recordOrigin>Created and edited in general conformance to MODS Guidelines (Version 3.5).</recordOrigin>
   </recordInfo>
</mods>