<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="3.5" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd"><titleInfo><title>H. Clay Evans, 1843-1921</title></titleInfo><typeOfResource>still image</typeOfResource><genre authority="dct">still image</genre><genre>special proofs</genre><subject><topic>Photographs.</topic></subject><subject><geographic>Chattanooga (Tenn.)</geographic></subject><subject><topic>Evans, H. Clay (Henry Clay), 1843-1921</topic></subject><subject><topic>Government and Politics.</topic></subject><subject><topic>Education.</topic></subject><subject><geographic>The Development of the Industrial United States (1870-1900).</geographic></subject><subject><geographic>Tennessee -- Franklin County.</geographic></subject><note>"Hon." H. Clay Evans was born in 1843 in Pennsylvania, and moved to Wisconsin with his parents in 1844. He served in the Union Army during the Civil War. After his service he moved to Chattanooga and served two terms as mayor beginning in 1881. Evans helped to organize the public-school system of Chattanooga, and served as the first school commissioner. He was elected to congress in 1889, but was not re-elected. He served as the first Assistant Postmaster General from 1891-1893. After an unsuccessful run for Governor of Tennessee, Evans was appointed Commissioner of Pensions from 1897 to 1902. Evans chose to enter the diplomatic service with an appointment as United States consul general to London, England from that point until 1905. Upon his return, Evans was chosen as commissioner of health and education of Chattanooga in 1911. Evans died in Chattanooga, Tennessee on December 12, 1921.</note><note>The University of Tennessee Libraries (Knoxville, Tennessee) is the digital publisher.</note><identifier type="local">TU:DLC:Filename:0046_000050_000257_0000</identifier><relatedItem><titleInfo><title>Digital Collection: The Growth of Democracy in Tennessee: A Grassroots Approach to Volunteer Voices</title></titleInfo></relatedItem><language><languageTerm type="code">eng</languageTerm></language><accessCondition type="use and reproduction" xlink:href="http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/">Copyright Undetermined</accessCondition><location><url access="object in context" usage="primary display">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A11768</url><url access="preview">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A11768/datastream/TN/view</url></location></mods>