<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"
      xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
      version="3.5"
      xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd">
   <titleInfo>
      <title>Monument of Sam Davis, Confederate Hero, Pulaski, Tenn. - 2658</title>
   </titleInfo>
   <typeOfResource>still image</typeOfResource>
   <genre authority="dct">still image</genre>
   <genre>postcards</genre>
   <subject>
      <topic>United States History Civil War, 1861-1865 Monuments.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Confederate States of America History.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <geographic>Pulaski (Tenn.) -- History</geographic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Wars and Military.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <geographic>The Great Depression and World War II (1929-1945).</geographic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <geographic>Tennessee -- Giles County.</geographic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Postcards.</topic>
   </subject>
   <subject>
      <topic>Davis, Sam.</topic>
   </subject>
   <note>2 tifs. A postcard of a monument of Sam Davis in front of the Giles County Courthouse. The statute features a sculpture of a young man standing defiantly and wearing a hat; it is inscribed with confederate flags and bears plaques with information about Davis and his execution. Davis was known as the "boy hero of the Confederacy," and was a private in the first Tennessee Volunteer infantry in 1861, and was captured in 1863 in possession of Union battle plans. In addition to the monument in Pulaski, there is a statue of Davis at the Tennessee state capitol in Nashville. The postcard reads: "Monument of Sam Davis, Confederate Hero, Pulaski, Tenn." The verso reads: "Dear Ruth, How are you all? We are fine. If nothing happens we are coming to church Sunday and will be out to see you after church. If we don't come you will know we couldn't get a way out. Love, Edith." It was sent to Mrs. Thomas Glover, Route 1, Pulaski, Tennessee. The time stamp reads Pulaski, Tenn. April 17 11:30 AM 1943. The card lists Silvercraft--made by Dexter Press, Pearl River, N.Y. And has a one cent stamp featuring the Statue of Liberty and the words Industry, Agriculture for Defense.</note>
   <note>The University of Tennessee Libraries (Knoxville, Tennessee) is the digital publisher.</note>
   <identifier type="local">TU:DLC:Filename:0096_000050_000213_0000</identifier>
   <relatedItem>
      <titleInfo>
         <title>Digital Collection: The Growth of Democracy in Tennessee: A Grassroots Approach to Volunteer Voices</title>
      </titleInfo>
   </relatedItem>
   <language>
      <languageTerm type="code">eng</languageTerm>
   </language>
   <accessCondition type="use and reproduction"
                    xlink:href="http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/">Copyright Undetermined</accessCondition>
   <location>
      <url access="object in context" usage="primary display">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A12149</url>
      <url access="preview">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A12149/datastream/TN/view</url>
   </location>
   <recordInfo>
      <recordContentSource>University of Tennessee, Knoxville. Libraries</recordContentSource>
      <languageOfCataloging>
         <languageTerm authority="iso639-2b" type="code">eng</languageTerm>
      </languageOfCataloging>
      <recordOrigin>Created and edited in general conformance to MODS Guidelines (Version 3.5).</recordOrigin>
   </recordInfo>
</mods>