<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="3.5" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd"><titleInfo><title>Letters to The Guardian Pertaining to the Resignation of Rev. F. G. Smith from the Columbia Female Institute</title></titleInfo><typeOfResource>text</typeOfResource><genre authority="dct">text</genre><genre>periodical</genre><subject><geographic>Civil War and Reconstruction (1850-1877).</geographic></subject><subject><topic>Tennessee History.</topic></subject><note>From the March-April 1852 edition of The Guardian Letters and circulars written in support of Reverend Franklin Gillette Smith in the wake of accusations of his alleged improprieties with a female student, which led to a scandal causing Bishop Otey to demand his resignation. Columbia rallied in support of Smith, and Otey`s subsequent unpopularity led him to move his family to Memphis. The first letter was signed by over 50 people listed as "Patrons of the Institute" and over 170 "Citizens of Columbia." Sarah Ann Smith, the wife of Rev. Smith, wrote a letter to the editor of the local Maury Intelligencer, which is reprinted in The Guardian. Finally, there is a circular by various Commissioners who pledge to financially support a new female institute in or near Columbia to be run by Reverend Smith.</note><note>The University of Tennessee Libraries (Knoxville, Tennessee) is the digital publisher.</note><identifier type="local">TU:DLC:Filename:0098_000050_000211_0000</identifier><relatedItem><titleInfo><title>Digital Collection: The Growth of Democracy in Tennessee: A Grassroots Approach to Volunteer Voices</title></titleInfo></relatedItem><language><languageTerm type="code">eng</languageTerm></language><accessCondition type="use and reproduction" xlink:href="http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/">Copyright Undetermined</accessCondition><location><url access="object in context" usage="primary display">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A9888</url><url access="preview">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A9888/datastream/TN/view</url></location></mods>