<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="3.5" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd"><titleInfo><title>East Side Square, Pulaski, Tenn.</title></titleInfo><typeOfResource>still image</typeOfResource><genre authority="dct">still image</genre><genre>postcards</genre><subject><topic>Postcards.</topic></subject><subject><geographic>Pulaski (Tenn.)</geographic></subject><subject><topic>Trade, Business, and Industry.</topic></subject><subject><geographic>Postwar United States (1945-1970).</geographic></subject><subject><geographic>Tennessee -- Giles County.</geographic></subject><subject><topic>East Side Square, Pulaski, Tennessee.</topic></subject><note>2 tifs. A postcard of the East Side Square, Pulaski, Tennessee. The street scene features a row of shops with storefronts below long, tall windows and buildings above. The street is shared by horses and automobiles, and a few shoppers enter the bank on the end of the block. The card is a black and white photograph with a blue sky added in the background. The time stamp on the front of the card reads Tucson, Ariz. Mar 4 3:30 PM 196-. The verso note reads "there. Clear skies yesterday and today, but rain over the coast. Guess we will get the storm later. The west side of the Sacramento river had gone over its banks - lots of floods. This card must be an 'oldie'. As ever, G." The card was sent to Dorothy Haught in Yuma Arizona after a scratched out address to Tucson. It was published by S. Issacs and Son. Pulaski, Tenn. It was sent on a red two cent stamp featuring Thomas Jefferson and stamped "Fight Infantile Par--- Join March of Dimes." The time stamp reads in part Sacramento, Calif. 1958.</note><note>The University of Tennessee Libraries (Knoxville, Tennessee) is the digital publisher.</note><identifier type="local">TU:DLC:Filename:0096_000050_000233_0000</identifier><relatedItem><titleInfo><title>Digital Collection: The Growth of Democracy in Tennessee: A Grassroots Approach to Volunteer Voices</title></titleInfo></relatedItem><language><languageTerm type="code">eng</languageTerm></language><accessCondition type="use and reproduction" xlink:href="http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/">Copyright Undetermined</accessCondition><location><url access="object in context" usage="primary display">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A12167</url><url access="preview">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A12167/datastream/TN/view</url></location></mods>