<mods xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="3.5" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.loc.gov/mods/v3 http://www.loc.gov/standards/mods/v3/mods-3-5.xsd"><titleInfo><title>Postcard of the "Fairview" residence of William Jennings Bryan in Lincoln, Nebraska</title></titleInfo><typeOfResource>still image</typeOfResource><genre authority="dct">still image</genre><genre>postcards</genre><subject><topic>Popular Culture and Folklife.</topic></subject><subject><geographic>The Emergence of Modern America (1890-1930).</geographic></subject><note>A postcard issued by the Davis Acetylene Gas Generator Company of the "Fairview" residence of William Jennings Bryan in Lincoln, Nebraska. The home was victorian in style and the image shows Bryan sitting on a bench in the foreground. The caption reads "'Fairview,' Residence of William Jennings Bryan, Lincoln, Neb. Lighted for Seven Years by a Davis Acetylene Gas Generator. Thousands of Residences, Business Blocks, Churches, Schools, Etc., are Lighted by Apparatus Manufactured by the Davis Acetylene Co., Elkhart, Ind." The back of the card has room for the client to fill out the size and energy needs of their home so they can send the card back to Davis for an estimate. The verso reads "Fill out and send to us for an estimate. Is your building a residence, store, factory, etc? How many rooms? Would you pipe the gas to barn? Would you use it for cooking? What illuminant do you use at present? Give your name. Town. State." The card was included in the collection to show the wealth and significance of the lawyer/politician who came to Dayton, Tennesee for the Scopes trial and the national importance of the trial.</note><note>The University of Tennessee Libraries (Knoxville, Tennessee) is the digital publisher.</note><identifier type="local">TU:DLC:Filename:0071_000050_000201_0000</identifier><relatedItem><titleInfo><title>Digital Collection: The Growth of Democracy in Tennessee: A Grassroots Approach to Volunteer Voices</title></titleInfo></relatedItem><language><languageTerm type="code">eng</languageTerm></language><accessCondition type="use and reproduction" xlink:href="http://rightsstatements.org/vocab/UND/1.0/">Copyright Undetermined</accessCondition><location><url access="object in context" usage="primary display">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A12003</url><url access="preview">https://digital.lib.utk.edu/collections/islandora/object/volvoices%3A12003/datastream/TN/view</url></location></mods>